### Contact

vivian.leung103@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vivian-ym-leung (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Strategic Communications Web Design Mobile Web Design

### Languages

English (Professional Working)
Chinese (Native or Bilingual)

# Vivian Leung

Digital professional

## Summary

Having 10 years' experience in multinational companies and agencies, I am an all-rounded digital specialist who is passionate for all things digital and social. I possess solid experience in e-Commerce and digital marketing, with 2 years' supervisory experience in Ernst & Young.

Moreover, my design background made me strong at visual communication and creative thinking. Interestingly, I have also developed an analytical mind-set through on-the-job experience. I like to study people's behaviour whenever I face an issue. I always ask "who, what, why, how" to gather data, then decode the message to form a meaningful picture. There are lots of possibilities unleashing the big data. It is the reason why I enjoy working in digital role for various industries.

### Experience

Societe Generale
Digital Communications Specialist
April 2017 - June 2022 (5 years 3 months)
Hong Kong

### Christie's

Web Producer (Digital Media and e-Commerce) March 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 4 months) Hong Kong

### **AXA**

Digital Marketing Manager October 2014 - March 2015 (6 months)

### EY

Asia-Pacific Digital Production Lead August 2010 - October 2014 (4 years 3 months)

Page 1 of 2

Oxfam Hong Kong
Digital Communications Officer
September 2006 - August 2010 (4 years)

New Digital Noise Designer October 2004 - June 2006 (1 year 9 months)

### Education

Seneca College

Diploma, Computer Programming · (September 2022 - April 2024)

Hong Kong Baptist University

Bachelor of Social Science (Hons) in Communication, Digital Graphic Communication · (2001 - 2004)